http://www.chronolux.com/privacy.php

Site Currency:
---Category---
Armand Nicolet» Hunter » J09 » L06 » M02 » M03 » S05 Baume & Mercier Watches» Capeland » Hampton City » Hampton Milleis » Hampton Spirit BulgariConcord WatchesCorum» Admirals Cup » Bubble »» Bubble Automatic »» Bubble Chrono »» Bubble Midsize »» Bubble Mini »» Bubble XL » Buckingham Daniel Roth Watches» Ladies Ebel Watches» 1911 » Beluga » Classic Wave » Discovery » Ladies » Sport Classic » Sport/Sportwave » Tarawa » Type-E » Voyager EdoxEterna WatchesFortisFrédérique ConstantGeorge Nelson design by Vitra» Desk Clocks » Wall clocks Golana WatchesHanhartIWC Watches» Ingenieur » Pilot » Portofino » Portuguese Jaeger LeCoultreJunghansLouis ErardMaurice Lacroix» Ladies » Les Classiques » Masterpiece » Masterpiece Manufacture Collection » Miros » Pontos MeisterSingerOmega WatchesOris WatchesPaul PicotPequignet WatchesPorsche Design WatchesRaymond WeilRolexSchaumburg WatchTAG Heuer Watches» Carrera » Monaco U-Boat WatchesUnion GlashütteUniversal GenéveVintage and Pre-ownedVulcainZenith Watches» Ladies
---Price---
0-1500
1501-3000
3001-5000
5001-7500
7501-10000
10000+
---Style---
Home
»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Statement of Intent
From time to time, you may be asked to submit personal information
about yourself (e.g. name and email address etc) in order to receive or
use services on our website, or when submitting support requests or
general queries.
By entering your details in the fields
requested, you enable Chronolux and its service providers to provide you
with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal
information, we will treat that information in accordance with this
policy. Our services are designed to give you the information that you
want to receive. We will act in accordance with current legislation and
aim to meet current Internet best practice.
When you supply any
personal information to Chronolux for whatever reason we have legal
obligations towards you in the way we deal with that data. We must
collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use
it (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are
requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the
information on to anyone else. In general, any information you provide
to us will only ever be used within our company and by its service providers.
It will never be supplied to anyone outside the company without first
obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to
disclose it.
Also, if you post or send offensive or inappropriate
content anywhere on or to our website, we can use whatever information
that is available to us about you to stop such behaviour. This may
include informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school
or e-mail provider about the content and your behaviour.
We will
hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the
service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose
has been met. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is
held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
If
you are notified on our site that your information may be used to allow
Chronolux to contact you for "service administration purposes", this
means that we may contact you for a number of purposes related to the
service you have signed up for. For example, we may wish to provide you
with password reminders or notify you that the particular service has
been suspended for maintenance.
Although we prepare a quartery newsletter, we will not contact you for promotional
purposes, such as notifying you of improvements to the service or new
services unless you specifically agree to be contacted for such purposes
at the time you submit your information on the site, or at a later time
if you sign up specifically to receive such promotional information.
Shopping
All Products
Our Watches
Categories and Products
Shopping Cart
Member
Login
Register
Zenith Watches
Disclosure Policy: All brand names, logos, watch images and trademarks used on the Chronolux.com website are the property of their respective owners and are used on this website and in posts for identification purposes only. We would like to point out that the reviews presented here are solely the views of Chronolux.com authors.  Chronolux.com team is not liable for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use. We are not an official dealer for the products listed here and have no affiliation with the manufacturer or received any type of remuneration to write a review.
Copyright © 2005 - 2016 Chronolux.com. All Rights Reserved. [Chronolux lists authentic Swiss and German Luxury Watches for sale.]
